ACTWU Communications and Public Relations Department Burt Beck Files 5619/027
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- New York State Official Directory Union Made Products and Services, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Official Directory of Union Made Products and Services, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Item is in English.
- Nagoya, Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
  English and Japanese
  - Item 1: Nagoya, Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    By City of Nagoya. Map. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Nagoya, Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    By City of Nagoya. Map. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Nagoya, Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Item is in English;Japanese.
  - Item 4: Nagoya, Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Copy 2. Item is in English;Japanese.
  - Item 5: Nagoya, Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Copy 3. Item is in English;Japanese.
- The Nation, 1976; Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
  September-October
  - Item 1: The Nation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    By ACWA. v.223: no. 14 (1976: Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Nation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    By ACWA. v.223: no.13 (1973: oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Nation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    By ACWA. v.223: no.11 (1976: oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Nation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    By ACWA. v.223: no.9 (1976: Sept.). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Nation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    By ACWA. v.223: no.8 (1976: Sept.). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Nation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    By ACWA. v.223: no.7 (1976: Sept.). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Nation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    By ACWA. v.223: no. 6 (1976: Sept.). Item is in English.
- The Nation, 1976; Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
  November- December
  - Item 1: The Nation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
    By ACWA. v.223: no.18 (1976: Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Nation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
    By ACWA. v.223: no.17 (1976: Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Nation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
    By ACWA. v.223: no.16 (1976: Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Nation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
    By ACWA. v.223: no.22 (1976: Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Nation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
    By ACWA. v.223: no.20 (1976: Dec.). Item is in English.
- The Nation, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: The Nation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
    By ACWA. v.224: no.12 (1977: Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Nation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
    By ACWA. v.224: no.1 (1977: Jan.). Item is in English.
- New Directions for a New City Texas AFL-CIO Convention, 1973; Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: New Directions for a New City, Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
- The New Republic, 1976-1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: The New Republic, Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
    March. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The New Republic, Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
    January. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The New Republic, Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Item 4: The New Republic, Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Item 5: The New Republic, Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Dec. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The New Republic, Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Rosemary Puglio Ritvo and Sondra Gash. Emma Goldman, Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Emma Goldman, Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    By Rosemary Puglia Ritvo with Sondra Gash. An Original Screenplay. Item is in English.
- Pamphlets, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 2: A Brief History of the Amalgamated, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    By Burt Beck. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Welcome to the ACTWU Second Constitutional Convention, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 4: Fabric of Injustice, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 5: The Battle of the Boycott, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    By Kenny Lapides. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Amalgamated Welfare Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 7: The Amalgamated Health Centers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 8: Gloves Fashion and Etiquette, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    By Edith Heal. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Valentin Jacob Thomas Wertheimer: A Celebration of his Life, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 10: Lebanon 82: Genocide, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 11: In Memoriam: Emil Rieve, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 12: Resolution on the Farah Strike, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 13: Sisters and Brothers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 14: Sisters and Brothers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 15: Two Eras of Amalgamated Progress, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 16: A Tribute to the Farah Workers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    By ACWA. Program. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Amalgamated Song Book, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 18: What is At Stake in the Stevens-Union Struggle?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 19: What is At Stake in the Stevens-Union Struggle?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: What is At Stake in the Stevens-Union Struggle?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Medal for a Union, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    By ILGWU. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: 28th Biennial Convention, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 23: How to Dress for a Depression, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 24: To Build a New World, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    By Thomas Brooks. Item is in English.
- Paul Newton Poling. For the Defense of Farah Workers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: For the Defense of Farah Workers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Item 2: For the Defense of Farah Workers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Photo Copy. Item is in English.
- The Prize Award Program of the Sidney Hillman Foundation 1950-1985, Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: The Prize Award Program of the The Sidney Hillman Foundation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Item 2: The Prize Award Program of the The Sidney Hillman Foundation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Item 3: The Prize Award Program of the The Sidney Hillman Foundation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Research Department Reports, 1985; Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Research Department Reports, Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Report of Public Relations Department, Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Report of Public Relations Department, Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Item 2: Report of Public Relations Department, Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Responses of the El Paso Committee for Fairness at Farah, 1973; Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Responses of the El Paso Committee for Fairness at Farah, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Resolutions. 29th Biennial Convention, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Resolutions. 29th Biennial Convention, Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Item 2: Resolutions. 29th Biennial Convention, Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Rub Sheet. Report on Union Busters, 1982; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
  July
  - Item 1: Rub Sheet. Report on Union Busters, Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Second Session of the 92nd Congress, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: The Advance. Second Session of the 92nd Congress, Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Jacob Sheinkman. Workers at Farah Seek Justice, Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Workers at Farah Company Seek Justice, Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
    By Jacob Sheinkman. Item is in English.
- Las Siguientes Modificaciones de la Constitucion, 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
  Spanish
  - Item 1: Las Siguientes Modificaciones de la Constitucion, Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
    By ACTWU. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: Las Siguientes Modificaciones de la Constitucion, Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
    By ACTWU. Copy 2. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 3: Las Siguientes Modificaciones de la Constitucion, Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Item 4: Las Siguientes Modificaciones de la Constitucion, Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
    By ACTWU. Copy 3. Item is in Spanish.
- Stevens Organizers, 1978; Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Stevens Organizer, Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
    By ACTWU. v.1: no.4 (1978: May). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Stevens Organizer., Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
    By ACTWU. v.1: no.4 (1978: May). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Stevens Organizer, Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
    By ACTWU. v.1: no.4 (1978: May). Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Stevens Organizer, Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
    By ACTWU. v.1: no.5 (1978: July). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Stevens Organizer, Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
    By ACTWU. v.1: no.5 (1978: July). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Stevens Organizer, Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
    By ACTWU. v.1: no.5 (1978: July). Copy 3. Item is in English.
- Summary of Legal Developments at Farah, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Summary of Legal Developments at Farah Manufacturing Company, Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Textile Week, 1982-1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Textile Week, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By McGraw Hill. v.5: no.41 (1982: Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Textile Week, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By McGraw Hill. v.5: no.42 (1982: Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Textile Week, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By McGraw Hill. v.5: no. 43 (1982: Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Textile Week, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By McGraw Hill. v.5: no.44 (1982: Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Textile Week, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By McGraw Hill. v.5: no. 45 (1982: Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Textile Week, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By McGraw Hill. v.5: no. 46 (1982: Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Textile Week, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Item 8: Textile Week, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By McGraw Hill. v.5: no. 47 (1982: Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Textile Week, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By McGraw Hill. v.5: no. 48 (1982: Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Textile Week, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By McGraw Hill. v.5: no. 49 (1982: Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Textile Week, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By McGraw Hill. v.6: no.1 (1982: Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Textile Week, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By McGraw Hill. v.6: no.2 (1983: Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Textile Week, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By McGraw Hill. v.6: no.3 (1983: Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Textile Week, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By McGraw Hill. v.6: no. 4 (1983: Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Textile Week, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By McGraw Hill. v.6: no.5 (1983: Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Textile Week, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By McGraw Hill. v.6: no.6 (1983: Feb.). Item is in English.
- This is Amalgamated, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: This is the Amalgamated, Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Viva La Huelga. Farah Strike Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.4. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.5. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.6. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.7. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.8. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.9. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.10. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.11. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.12. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.13. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.14. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.15. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.16. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.17. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.18. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.19. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.20. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.21. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.22. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.23. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.24. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.25. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.26. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.27. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.28. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.29. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.30. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. n.31. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACWA. April. Item is in English.
- Viva La Huelga. Farah Strike Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.26; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.27; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Item 4: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.28; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.29; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.30; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.31; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Strike is Ended, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Item 9: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.8; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.9; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.10; Copy 2. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 12: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.11; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.12; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.13; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.14; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.15; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.16; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.17; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.18; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.19; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.20; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Item 23: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.21; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.22; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.23; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.24; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.25; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.1; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.2; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.3; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.4; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.5; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By aCWA. n.6; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    By ACWA. n.7; Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Viva La Huela. Farah Strike Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
  Copy #3
  - Item 1: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.1; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.2; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Item 4: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.4; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.5; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.6; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.7; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.8; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.9; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.10; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.11; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.12; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.13; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.14; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.15; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.16; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.17; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.18; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.19; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. N.20; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.21; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.22; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.23; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.24; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.25; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.26; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.27; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.28; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.29; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. n.30; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Viva La Huelga, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Item 32: The Strike is Ended, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACWA. Copy 3. Item is in English.
- Winning in Washington, 1982; Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Winning in Washington, Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Item 2: Winning in Washington, Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Working in Hospitals: Then and Now, 1976; Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
  September
  - Item 1: Working in Hospitals: Then and Now, Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Jacob S. Potofsky Retirement Scrapbook, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Jacob S. Potofsky Retirement Scrapbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
- ACWA News Press Release, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  May
- ACWA News Press Releases, 1972; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
- ACWA News Press Releases, 1973; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
- ACWA News Press Releases, 1974; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
- ACWA News Press Releases, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
- ACWA News Press Releases, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
- ACTWU News Press Releases, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
- ACTWU News Press Releases, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
- ACTWU News Press Releases, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Folder #1
- ACTWU News Press Releases, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Folder #2
- ACTWU News Press Releases, 1979; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
- ACTWU News Press Releases, 1980; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
- ACTWU News Press Releases, 1981; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
- ACTWU News Press Releases, 1982; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
- ACTWU News Press Releases, 1983; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
- ACTWU News Press Releases, 1984; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
- ACTWU News Press Releases, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  No Dates
- AFL-CIO Press Releases, 1972-1974; Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Press Releases General, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Press Releases Special to El Paso Media, 1972-1974; Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Items Written for Labor Unity, 1982; Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Items Written for Labor Unity, 1983; Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Items Written for Labor Unity, 1984; Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Folder 1 of 2
- Items Written for Labor Unity, 1984; Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
  Folder 2 of 2
- Clippings, 1962-1970; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Clippings, 1972; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  April-July